(Sheldon:)Amy Farrah Fowler,
(Sheldon:)and Penny.
(Amy:)Yes!
(Amy:)He had you in the other car,
but I got you upgraded.
(Penny:)Yay!
(Sheldon:)She made the case
that if we break down
(Sheldon:)in the middle of nowhere,
your Nebraska backwoods skills
(Sheldon:)and brawny hands
will give us the best chance
(Sheldon:)to survive in the wild.
(Penny:)Brawny?
(Leonard:)They're bigger
than mine.
(Sheldon:)Red Leader to Red Five,
come in.
(Sheldon:)Howard, you promised.
(Bernadette:)WOLOWITZ
Fine. Red Five to Red Leader.
(Howard(voice):)What do you want now?
It's 11:15. I'm requesting your
quarter-hourly location update.
(Howard:)Still right behind you.
(Sheldon:)Copy that, Red Five.
(Sheldon:)Radio contact is sufficient.
(Sheldon:)No need to extend
your middle finger.